Now, we'll study one of the ways to measure how good a model is,
现在我们来学习衡量模型性能的一种方式
called that the accuracy.
称为“准确度”
The accuracy is the answer to the question,
准确度就是下面这个问题的答案
在所有就诊者中 我们正确分类的有多少？
"Out of all the patients, how many did we classify correctly?"
The answer is, the ratio between the number of
答案就是 正确分类的点数和总点数
correctly classified points and the number of total points.
之间的比例
In this example, we can see that we have correctly classified 9,000 patients,
在这个例子中 可以看到我们正确分类了 9,000 名就诊者
which is a sum of 1,000 healthy and 8,000 sequence.
是 1,000 名健康就诊者和 8,000 名患病者之和
So, the accuracy is this number divided by the total number of patients, which is 10,000.
所以准确度是这个数字
除以就诊者总数 也就是 10,000
所得的准确度为 90%
This gives us an accuracy of 90%.
在 sklearn 中 使用 accuracy_score 函数可以很容易地计算
Accuracy can easily be calculated as you can learn by using the accuracy score function.
准确度
Now, let's see how much is the accuracy of the spam detector model?
现在我们来看看 垃圾邮件检测器模型的准确度是多少
This is the answer to the question,
也就是下面这个问题的答案 在所有电子邮件中
"Out of all the emails, how many did we classify correctly?"
有多少是正确分类的？
Since we have correctly classified 800 out of the 1,000 emails,
由于我们在 1,000 封邮件中正确分类了 800 封
then the answer is 80%.
所以答案是 80%
下面来检测下你的知识掌握情况
Now, let's test your knowledge.
In this model, what is the accuracy?
在这个模型中 准确度是多少？
Please write the numbers of percentage.
So, a number between 0 and 100.
请写下一个百分比 数字介于 0 到 100 之间
This number can have decimals.
可以包含小数